Starlight Glimmer, you always said I
didn't do enough. Well, today is the day
I prove just how wrong you are.
Mary, how did you get in my house?
I used your doggy door.
You saw a hole in my front door. Look, I
made both of us breakfast. It's still
hot. And and I even did your coffee the
way you like it.
Okay.
Why are you being weird? Are you fishing
for praise or something?
Do you want me to eat your cute
butthole?
>> I was trying to make you happy.
>> Oh, so now you want to make me happy,
you freaking [__]
Now look what you've done. You're making
a mess of my kitchen. I'm sorry. I'll
clean it up right away.
>> Actually, you should eat that. You know,
since you worked so hard on it.
>> I I don't think
>> you're thinking now. Oh my. This is a
big day for you.
Eat the pancake, Mary.
Oh, I get it. You want another form of
cake? Well, I'm happy to oblige you,
Mary. And by oblige, I mean blast a
massive fat one in your freaking face.
>> Is Is that a black Philly? I can't
believe they let something like that
into the Philly Scouts. The Philly
Scouts really have fallen off.
>> Thank you for your patronage.
>> Mom, why won't any pony buy my cookies?
Is it because I'm black?
>> You're never going to win me that sweep
stakes trip if you can't even sell a
single box. Pack up your things and
follow me. We're going home where I can
beat you up as much as I want behind
closed doors.
Hey Jinx, do you want to see something
super cool?
>> Did you see that? Only professional male
ponies can put mail in the mailbox
without touching the rim. Maybe one day
you'll be able to do it, too. When
you're not just some worthless
paraplegic piece of crap. Quit shoving
all of the main six's mail into my
mailbox derpy. We count as individual
citizens
>> or else what you nerd. You got to come
over here and [__] us
>> or else. Well, just stop doing it. Okay.
Hey, Twilight. Derpy dropped your mail
off at my house again. I hope you don't
mind, but I already read it. Your
parents invited you over for dinner.
>> You opened my mail? That's a federal
offense.
>> Yeah, I thought there would be money in
it. So, back on topic, I figured I would
go, too, since you and me barely hang
out together these days. Oh, well, I
don't really want you to come. You can
go home now. Thanks for giving me my
mail. I can't believe this [__] It's
already going to be hell trying to
introduce my parents to Flawless. Now,
on top of that, you want to drag your
stupid ass sister into this, too.
>> She is not stupid, and she deserves to
be a part of the family gatherings the
same as me.
>> Yeah. And Grandma Velvet is going to
adore me. I am literally perfect.
Well, look who it is. Twilight Sparkle,
I hope you finally come to apologize for
the [__] you pulled back in elementary.
What's she talking about? It's a school
thing. You had to be there.
>> You had to be there.
>> I had to be there. You had to be there.
Actually, we came to invite Marionette
to a family dinner with my parents. Wow,
inviting her without me in front of me.
That's so cruel, Twilight, even for you.
But I'll forgive her, baby. I always
forgive the ones who hurt me. You know
that all too well, don't you? Um, I'd
really like to go Twilight, but I sort
of already promised Starlight that I
would spend the day with her.
She can come too.
>> Absolutely not. This dinner is about our
family unit. She'll ruin the whole
dynamic.
>> Twilight, please. Trixie doesn't like
the pink [__] either. But the pink
[__] is a very important friend to
marry.
>> See that? She gets it.
>> Honey, have you seen my wedding ring?
>> [__] the [__] do you think? I am a
man. I don't look at jewelry, especially
rings made for girls out of principle
because I am not a female, but a strong,
powerful male. I think I lost it when I
threw away all of your empty beer
bottles this morning.
>> You what? [__] that ring cost me $14
whole dollars.
>> Exactly. $14, which is why I'm sure it's
cheap enough for you to buy me a new
one.
>> Lady, do I look like I have $14? Where
did you last see it?
>> How should I know? Maybe if you weren't
so drunk all the time and actually got
me a real ring for a change, this
wouldn't keep happening.
Did you seriously just hit me over $14?
>> And I'll do it again, too. Now go to
Taco Bell to get some lucha boxes for
dinner.
>> Dad, can you please not punch mom in
front of my wife over 14 stupid dollars?
>> Boy, I can do whatever the hell I damn
well please in my own damn house. And
$14 isn't stupid. It's groceries for the
week if you shop smart, which you
clearly never have to do because you
married into royalty.
>> Don't you bring my wife's royal lineage
into this. You started.
>> Look, every pony. Twilight is here and
she brought guests.
Twilight dear, it's been a long while.
Welcome home.
>> Too long, mother. And there's some
really special ponies here that I'd love
for you to finally meet.
>> Sweet Celestia, one of you smell like
[__] I think it's the blue one. [__]
you stink like hell. Guest bedrooms
upstairs. Keep the window open, though,
so you don't suffocate the whole house
with your unwashed but crack. [__] are
you just going to let the door hang open
all night? The air conditioner is on,
and I'm not paying to cool the whole
damn neighborhood. Go shut the damn
door.
>> It's literally snowing. Why do you need
the AC on?
>> Don't get snappy with me, you ugly
[__]
>> Don't you dare talk to my daughter like
that.
>> Your daughter?
>> Um, I I mean, yes, my daughter
temporarily. I I adopted her. Okay, so
back off,
shall we? Uh, hey, Trixie, you did take
a bath or something before we got here,
right? Are you suggesting that Trixie
smells like crap?
>> Wait, you really can't smell yourself?
>> The only scent Trixie notices is the
sweet aroma of victory and adoration
from her fans. Okay, maybe she does
[__] stink. Trixie hasn't been making
much money lately. Times are tough and
she had to cut back on a lot of [__]
including baths. She can only afford to
bathe once a year right now. Trixie only
knows it's time to wash when the leaves
fall. How long have you been doing this?
14 years. Please don't tell your
parents. Trixie really wants them to
like her.
>> It's probably a little late for that. We
already smelled you.
>> Hey, you doing all right?
>> The great and powerful Trixie has been
through many trials and tribulations,
but she never had any pony's dad call
her [__] smelly.
>> Look, I'm sorry about what happened
downstairs. My dad was out of line, but
he's like that with everyone because he
drinks a lot, so don't take it
personally.
>> Hey, Twilight, your mom said I should
apologize, but I don't want to do that.
So, I thought of a compromise. And if
you have your friend suck my balls, I
would be willing.
>> That's going to be a no. Sorry, Dad.
>> I'll give you $8.
>> Mr. Nightlight, you're making me feel
uncomfortable. Can you get out?
>> The only pony that should feel
uncomfortable in this room is me because
I have a stranger in my house. I'm going
downstairs. You are a [__]
>> Sparkle, is it normal for one of your
guests to start re-evaluating their life
choices that lead them here?
>> Don't worry. He does that with every
pony because he drinks a lot.
>> Mom, I just can't stand seeing you put
up with dad anymore. He doesn't treat
you the way you deserve. You need
someone who would actually treasure you.
>> Shining, you're my son. We shouldn't be
talking like this.
>> I know I'm your son. That's exactly why
I'd never betray you. I know what makes
you happy, Mom. You deserve an expensive
candle lit dinner at Red Lobster.
Not lukewarm tacos because dad was too
lazy to help you cook. Taco Bell is
straight cheeks.
>> Don't listen to him, Miss Velvet. Taco
Bell [__] slaps. The Doritos Locos
Taco Supreme is an S
>> fast food item.
>> Shining. We shouldn't be doing this.
This is wrong. We're family.
>> Maybe we're not just family, Mom. Maybe
we're two lost souls who desperately
need someone else to cling to.
>> Gee, Willigus, bro, you should come look
at this really cool rock I found in the
backyard.
Where's the cool rock?
>> Shining armor. Why the [__] were you
trying to swap spit with our mom?
>> There is no rock out here. You lied to
me.
>> Shining.
>> Okay, okay, I admit it. It was a moment
of weakness. I got carried away. She
just looked really sad crying in her
room with the Taco Bell party pack. What
was I supposed to do? Honestly, I wasn't
really thinking about the fact that, you
know, she's mom.
>> Oh my god, bro. We're her children, not
her rebound. You don't get to step up
when dad is being a [__]
>> Please don't tell dad or my wife about
this. If they find out, I'll get
grounded.
>> G Willicker. Stranger. You look just
like my plushy. He's really soft, except
for when he gets crusty. Say, would
either of you like to buy a box of Thin
Mints from our Philly scout troop? We're
trying to win a sweep stakes.
>> No.
>> Oh, okay.
Wowzers. A gummy worm.
>> How do you know that was a gummy worm?
>> It wasn't.
Do you always put random things in your
mouth?
>> Uh-huh. Sucking on things is fun.
Sometimes it's tasty, but most of the
time it's icky. But my mom is always
telling me to try new things.
>> I don't think she means eating stuff off
the floor.
>> Can you please leave? Black ponies are
not permitted in this gated community
after nightfall.
>> Holy [__] Are you all right?
>> Wow, that ice almost killed me just now.
Oh my god. If I die before meeting my
nerdy white boy, I'm going to be so mad.
>> I'm taking the Taco Bell out of the
microwave. Can you go fetch the kids and
tell them it's time to eat?
>> I don't know. Can you wait until I am
done? Anyone with eyes can see I'm
obviously drinking beer.
>> Okay, so maybe our first impression
didn't go so well. You know why they
said you were adopted though, right?
Because they're ashamed of us. Twilight
and Trixie don't really love us. They
never did. Twilight had to lie just to
justify why we're even here. They lied
because they want the family to know we
don't belong.
>> [__] Get off the pot, [__] Daddy got
a poopy.
>> And we don't. But there's a way we can.
We can make them obey us. You heard what
that man called you, right? Ugly [__]
You don't have to take that. Kill him.
>> Kill him.
>> Kill him. And they'll all know we're the
ones in control.
It's nice to finally have the family
together sharing a meal. This is what
life's all about.
>> Would be better if we weren't locked in
a concrete box with a stinky magician.
>> May Stinky, I mean Trixie, be excused.
No, Trixie. Actually, you may not. We're
going to sit right here and have a
wholesome family meal.
>> The hell? What? You wearing a mask at my
table for [__] You think you're better
than the rest of us?
>> Um, you see, Mr. Light, I have
thirdderee burns all across my face.
Showing it off makes me feel
uncomfortable. Oh, for Celestia's sake,
Mary. No one here cares about your
scars. Take it off and eat. I would
really rather not. Starlight, stop it. I
do not consent to this.
This is it. It's over. They're all going
to hate me now. Any chance I had of a
happy life with them is?
>> You're You're not going to turn away
from me.
>> Oh, there's nothing to be ashamed of,
Mary. You look fine.
>> Great. Now, not only has my wife lost
her wedding ring in the trash, now the
kitchen smells like a burnt paper bag
full of [__] Thanks a lot, kid. We
vegged a total stinker on one side and a
[__] on fire on the other.
>> Dad, that's enough. You don't get to sit
here and humiliate everyone when your
hair looks like that. You're just being
a bully.
>> Oh, yes, I can. This is my house,
Velvet. Tell our sexy son that I am
right.
>> Nightlight, maybe you could just
>> agree with me, [__] You're making me
angry.
>> That's horrible. She's not even allowed
to think for herself around you.
>> How does it make you feel to not have
the privilege of being a man? I hope it
pisses you off.
>> You call it privilege to be born a
stallion, but that's only because you
never had to fight to earn the ground
you walk on. Mares are constantly made
to struggle in a man's world. And yet,
we're still here. How does it make you
feel that every time you try to silence
us, our voices only grow louder like a
chorus? Yeah, Dad. Mares deserve
respect. Every bit as much as stallions.
>> God put mares on this planet to do two
things. Bitching and [__] And right
now you're doing a whole lot of
bitching. Maybe you aren't the man I
thought you were, son.
>> Are you calling me a [__] queer? I'll
beat your ass.
>> Oh, and is there something wrong with
that shining armor?
>> What? No. I think lesbians are hot. I
mean,
>> typical. Men are such pigs.
>> At least we aren't stinky.
>> Dad, that's rude. We all know Trixie
stinks, but you don't have to keep
pointing it out.
>> Let's all just settle down and enjoy our
food. Okay,
>> sniff my balls, lady. You're not the one
sitting directly across from a stinky
piece of [__]
>> That's enough out of you, Dad. Trixie
may not be your idea of the perfect
pony, but she's still my friend, and
she's worked super hard to get where
she's at. So, give her a little more
respect, will you?
>> But she is stinky.
>> No, she smells good. Maybe it's you who
should think about stepping into a
shower for a change, Dad. Because from
what I see, it's not Trixie that stinks.
It's your [__] attitude towards her.
>> Trixie is sorry if her smelly but crack
made you all sad. She'll just excuse
herself to the [__]
>> I got to go, too.
Look, Trixie, this violent beating of
your ass isn't personal, but Twilight
has to pay in some way for what she did
to me at school.
>> You speak of the marshmallow incident,
[__] That was over 20 years ago. All
those involved vowed never to speak of
such things again. Get away from the
door.
>> You're a [__] coward, just like you
were then.
>> Maybe I am, though. Be that as it may, I
will not discuss this with you at top
the [__] of my mother-in-law's
homestead. Your little surprise attack
failed. Now remove yourself from the
door and let me do my business in peace
before I [__] down your throat. But
knowing you, you might be into that
[__] you sick [__]
Yeah, you better walk away. Sorry, I was
in there for an hour and 45 minutes. It
was a double flusher.
>> We didn't even hear you flush once.
I'm going to put down this tip jar and
do some street magic while you guys eat
your Taco Bell. Feel free to give me
money.
>> What the [__] am I supposed to eat now?
Eat [__] gummy worms for dinner? Are
you kidding me? You know I don't know
how to cook. The house will be a mess
without you to clean. You know this is
[__] that you did this to me. I got
a little tickle in my throat. I don't
even know how to make a doctor's
appointment. You always did that for me.
What the [__] Are you serious?
on your face.
>> What you playing?
>> Just a game.
>> It looks fun. Can I play
>> single player? Sorry.
>> So, uh, what kind of things do you do in
this game?
Oh, just kill things.
>> I see.
>> What would you do?
Baby, it's getting late. Come to bed and
cuddle with me to prove that you
actually love me and didn't just
willingly murder my mother in cold blood
out of fear of her rejecting you because
you're covered in stinky, sweaty mar
smell particles. Give me a minute,
Sparkle. I need to renew my Xbox Game
Pass subscription. It's the one thing
aside from my cool hat that keeps me
going in these trying times. What? What
is this? Oh yeah, they raised the price
of Xbox Game Pass by 50% a few weeks
ago.
>> What? But what? What am I going to do,
Sparkle? I can't afford that. Why would
they do this to me? Twilight Sparkle.
>> How are you feeling, Mr. light.
>> Not good, doctor. I fear this is the
first problem in my life that a bottle
of beer or having a 49in penis can't
solve.
Damn, did you see that? What a [__]
dumper on that [__] Am I right, son?
You think she'll let us hit that [__]
together tomorrow if Velvet doesn't
survive through the night? Hey, can you
stay here with the family so I can go
home and get drunk?
>> The woman of your life is dying and all
you can think about is getting drunk.
>> Is that a bad thing?
You go and get drunk all you want. I'm
going to be there with my mom in her
final moments because that's what a man
does.
You know, I was I was actually excited
to meet you, to have someone who'd look
at me like I wasn't just some project of
Twilight and Trixie's mistake. Not that
I'm ever a mistake. I'm flawless.
I'm the best thing that ever happened to
this stupid family. I shine brighter
than all of you put together. But
>> but I wanted you to see that for
yourself.
>> I wanted you to see me.
>> And now now I don't know if you ever
will. You would have loved me. I know
you would have. Everyone does. But I
wanted you to say it just once.
Flawless. Oh wow. Didn't realize you
were spying, Twilight. You know, just
giving grandma the talk of her life.
Probably the best speech she'll never
hear. I didn't realize how much this
mattered to you. Well, duh. She's
technically my grandmother in a way.
Even if you lied and said I was adopted,
it' still be cool to know if she, you
know, wanted me. Flawless. I I never
should have said that. I told that lie
because I was scared. Scared of what my
parents might say about me being like
gay and [__] That I fell in love with a
mayor. Instead of telling them the truth
about who I am and who you and Trixie
were to me, I lied like a [__] I never
should have let my fear make you feel
unwanted. You and Trixie are the most
important things to me in this whole
heteronormative world.
>> So, the truth comes out. It's about damn
time. Now, I finally have an excuse to
disown you. You walk around parading
that washed up, smelly stage mare as
your wife, dragging in her creepy sister
and her lunatic girlfriend, and now you
want that abomination in this family.
You're just a no good, ungrateful little
[__] And your mom would be saying the
same thing if she were here.
>> Twilight.
>> Yes, Mom. It's me. I'm here.
>> Mom, there's something I need to
confess. That Trixie girl, she she's not
just my friend. She's my wife. and
flawless. She's our daughter.
>> Twilight, of course, I already knew
that. A mother knows these things, but
why in the world would you ever think
you had to hide something so important
from me?
>> Don't you turn your back on me,
Twilight.
>> You [__] shut my arm. I'll kill you.
I'll [__] kill all of you [__]
>> Daddy is mad and he's charging up for a
powerful attack to kill us all.
We're all back from using the hospital
bathroom to take shits.
>> This is bad. There are hundreds of
ponies in this hospital alone. If we
fight here, who knows how many lives
we'll be putting at risk.
>> Say no more love. We'll just have to
take this fight somewhere more empty.
Go. Teleportation spell.
>> Rarity's boutique. Nice thinking,
Trixie. Absolutely no pony comes to this
[__] hole and buys Rarity's ugly
clothes. Now why are you
>> flawless? We can't hold him. He's too
strong because he's drunk as [__] We
need you. But he's your father. You
don't realize what you're asking me to
do.
I know he's my family, but so are you.
You're part of our family. No matter
what he says.
>> Sweetie Bell run. He's flying right
towards your ass.
>> Oh my god.
>> Flawless. Why did you do that?
>> Yay! We did it.
You saved him. Even after what he did,
you actually saved him.
Well, I couldn't exactly let him die. I
mean, imagine how Twilight would feel.
She might have never spoken to us again.
>> You're truly something. You know, I'm
proud of you, Flawless.
>> Huh? What for?
>> You made the right call. You did what I
probably wouldn't have.
saving him.
>> I just did what I could to end it
without casualties.
>> Yes, that's the empathy you inherited
from Twilight. Something which I lack.
You see, I spent nearly all of my life
trying to prove I wasn't a loser.
>> Okay. But every time I failed,
>> okay, over and over again.
>> Okay. So, I gave up thinking that I
would never do anything right.
>> Okay. That is until you came along. When
I look at you, I realize something.
Despite the fact that I've made
mistakes, too many mistakes to count,
>> you're really just about the one and
only thing that I know I got right.
>> So, let's keep on getting better.
>> So, hang on.
Look how high we can fly. Look how high
we can fly. We can see everything. Look
up here in the sky. We've got the
perfect view together, me and you. Look
how high we can fly.
Words come so easily.
Hard to believe it's me. With every
breath, the feeling grows.
Take time to make time stop. Unclo, turn
off the clock. The less you try, the
more it grows.
I keep on rising up. No coming down. I
don't need to live in a fancy castle.
No, that isn't where I should be.
Open up my heart and where it leads I'll
follow.
I where I can be free.
fly. Look how high we can fly. We can
see everything from up here in the sky.
Look how high we can fly. Look how high
we can fly. We can surf on the wings.
Look how high we can fly.
This is my wife's wedding ring. But I
don't understand. Velvet accidentally
threw it away days ago. How did you ever
find it?
>> Well, it wasn't easy. I had to dig
through the dumpster each night.
Eventually, I found it stuck to some
toilet paper that was drenched in your
wet crap.
>> Wait, are you telling me that the reason
you smelled like [__] all week was
because you were digging through the
trash to help me?
>> Take care, Mr. Light.
>> Trixie, wait. I want to apologize for
the way I treated you. Twilight told me
about your rocky relationship with your
real daddy. If you ever need a cool
badass dude to, I don't know, teach you
how to pick up sexy [__] and
non-consensually slap their asses and
avoid jail time or something, don't be
afraid to give me a call. I'll keep that
in mind. Flawless. Come on down. We're
heading home.
Why are you smiling like that? Ponies
smile when they're happy. So, it stands
to reason that a bigger smile equals
more happiness. If I smiled big enough,
you'd know that I'm happy to be here
with you. Well, you know, normal ponies
don't smile with their teeth and gums
showing like they're in constant pain.
Try relaxing your face a little. You
don't have to force it.
Is Is this good?
No.
It's perfect.
Heat. Heat.
Heat. Heat. Heat.
Heat.
I am hunting
from the sky.
Heat.
Heat
up
here.